The rebels do not like Freyda, who they remember as their enemy. But there is a man who trusts her and could help her win their confidence. That man is Duncan, now confined in a prison and waiting to be taken to Talonguard. Freyda has to liberate him -- the sooner the better. The way to Duncan’s prison leads through the rebels’ lands, and they will surely attack her small force. The best way would be to seize one of the towns, hire reinforcements, and set Duncan free before the rebels can join their forces to rout Freyda.