Freyda releases Duncan (his escorts join her). She tells him that she wants to oppose Isabel. But she has to conceal herself. If Laszlo and Isabel learn of her deserting, they will kill her father Godric. Duncan offers a bolder way: seizing a port town, now held by Laszlo's troops, and sailing for the Empire to set Godric free. If both Godric's daughter and the renowned knight himself side with the Rebels, Isabel's reign will fall. Freyda agrees.