Shadow is strongest where there is little light, and luck favours Dark Elf fighters while they war in their vast caverns. But no one can tell what will happen when they stand in battle, on the surface, against the children of Light and Fire. Perhaps new allies will come to the aid of the clans of Ygg-Chall in this battle. Or perhaps they, too, are but pawns in the game that Order and Chaos have played since the day the world was made -- and they will be sacrificed accordingly.