The town of Horncrest, the capital of the Stag Duchy, has seen much lately.  It has seen numerous masters, the death of the butcher Laszlo, and now serves as the last stronghold of the rebels.  Rebels, of course, who oppose their Queen while not even suspecting who she really is. Ylaya and Isabel are headed there, hoping to tell the people of the Empire the truth about their ruler. Ylaya and Isabell must reach Horncrest within a week.