Located in the frontier between the Dwarven Kingdom and the lands of the Empire, Tor Hrall is a center of trade. This is the only Dwarven town where representatives of other races can be often met, all because of the commerce which makes the town’s living. In spite of its privileges, Tor Hrall keeps the prices low in its market, to stop the aliens from  rumoring about the Dwarves’ alleged niggardliness.