Oh dear, there's no peace and quiet in the Empire at all! They say some of the nobles are not happy with Isabel's rule -- like Lords Caldwell and Randall who are trying to put Andrei, Nicolai's nephew, on the throne.  The most daring are blaming Isabel for Nicolai's death, saying he died because of her recklessness. There was some rioting in Yellowdale, but Isabel quelled it quickly enough. But people still talk, and there are rumours aplenty.