The Fifth Eclipse War cost dearly to all members of the Grey Alliance. The border towns of the Griffin Empire are in ruins, and the Wizards of the League of Silver Cities are still counting their losses. The Elves of Irollan were not spared either, there is an urgent need to rebuild their ruined towns. With this in mind, King Alaron of the Elves has ordered the Ranger Ossir to the eastern border. His mission is to find the Tear of Asha, a powerful artifact that will help his people to rebuild their cities.