War is threatening, and the lands of Irollan will soon be invaded by the armies of the Necromancers -- even now they are massing near the borders.  Findan hopes to enlist the aid of the Emerald Dragons, who disappeared from Irollan after the War of the Grey Alliance.<br> But the task will not be easy as the Blazing Sands, the ancient home of the dragons, is under Demon control. Find Emerald dragons and assemble twenty of them in one army.