An ancient manuscript found and deciphered by Naadir revealed a mysterious portal to an ancient tomb.  The manuscript promised -- vaguely -- that remnants of the teachings of Sar-Elam annotated by Belketh lay there, it represented the only existent copy of such a document. The manuscript stated that the portal was guarded by an army of Spectral Dragons, and Naadir could never have imagined beating them in combat. He has no intention of fighting them, however, as some Necromancers are also skilled negotiators.