The death of Markal spelled the end of the short reign of the Necromancers. In some remote or hostile areas, however, Necromancers lived in relative peace with their neighbours and were spared the subsequent bloodletting. The Vale of Sorrow is one such place, and Giovanni hopes that it will stay that way. His hope is based on his alliance with Lady Ornella whose kin cursed her for loyally serving Queen Isabel and her twice-dead husband. The Necromancer hopes that using his alliance to his best advantage will let him make a stand for the Vale of Sorrow.