The Griffin Empire is falling apart. Refusing to accept the rule of Queen Isabel, some members of the nobility are openly opposing her. Her recent canonization has hardly helped matters, and they whisper that she has not been the same since her return from Sheogh.. No doubt these rebels will soon be dragged before a court of justice, which will inflict a harsh penalty on those who betray of the throne.