Victory is near! It is the year 843, and strengthened by an eclipse the Demonlords have invaded Ashan in great numbers. The Imperial capital of Falcon's Reach is surrounded and the hated Falcon dynasty is nearly extinct. The Demon Sovereign has all his attention focused on this campaign as he hopes to see the fulfillment of an ancient prophecy -- that the world of Men shall exist only so long as there is a Falcon heir. There is one small fly in the ointment, however, another legend states that the scions of Falcon shall never be defeated as long as they hold Falcon's Reach. With that in mind, the Sovereign has sent his loyal general, Jezebeth, to see to the end of the Falcons.