Hero name is a member of the Beastmaster/Hunter clan of dwarves; he is strong and inured to the extreme conditions of the Dwarven mountains (not many Dwarves venture outside their subterranean cities). His travels in the exterior have also made him friendly with other peoples, a fact that for some more conservative elements is equivalent to being tainted. Though an important and respected leader, Fabrice has problems with both his bluntness and his innocence. Having embarrassed the king once too often with his plain language and undiplomatic opinions, he has been more or less banished to the frontier where he is the captain of an important garrison. That way, the king's advisors managed to both put a reliable Dwarf in a strategic position, and remove a nuisance from the court.