Hyrkjolf is a town where warriors who are bent on becoming Berserkers undergo their last trials. The Rocks of Fury, a ridge of tremendous stones, are located near the town’s walls, and only a fighter who can cleave one of them with his bare hands is entitled to be called a Berserker. Not all can pass this test, but the flow of bold Dwarves who want to earn the title never stops -- and the town is never short of warriors, either.