The walls of Icegerd are magnificent mountains covered by ancient glaciers. Once upon a time they served as a shelter for rebellious Dwarves, and many warriors fell under these unassailable walls.  Though the the rebels -- short of food and supplies -- finally submitted to the winners, the walls remained.  Appreciating their defensive capabilites, King Tolghar ordered to build the town of Icegerd here.