Thorbjar’s frozen waterfall is a magnificent and beautiful sight. A pillar of water, glittering in the sun, it towers above the town, its summit disappearing in the clouds. Many Dwarves come to Thorbjar to feast their eyes upon this natural marvel. Few know, however, that the waterfall of K’arnar is also the town’s source of prosperity; deep in the thick of the mountain, hidden from an outsider’s view by the frozen column, there is another waterfall with fair crystals instead of ice.