Upon the death of Archmage Cyrus the role of Supreme Mage of the Circle was given to his son, Zehir. On Zehir’s right hand is the Ring of the Unrepentant, the magical artifact that leads to a dimension that became his father’s grave. Faced with difficult political and administrative tasks in rebuilding the Silver Cities, Zehir often wishes he had his father's shrewd diplomatic skills to help deal with other powerful mages -- his cantankerous co-rulers.