For hundreds of years no army dared to enter the lands of Grimheim, the Dwarven Kingdom.  Even those hungry for the riches of the Dwarven mines knew that the followers of Arkath make relentless enemies.  But now, war has come from where no one would ever expect it -- their old neighbours and allies, the Men of the Griffin Empire. It’s time for the Dwarves to remember their prowess as warriors, and to make sure their foes remember it as well.