Vemsdal was the Dwarven Kingdom’s first capital, beseiged during a time of clan infighting. That war, which took the lives of many renowned warriors, ended in a grand tournament whose winner became the founder of the current ruling dynasty. Though the winner left the town and founded a new capital, Vemsdal remains a magnet for heroes. Legend has it that a Dwarf who begins his or her service in Vemsdal can reach similarly lofty heights.