I’ve heard some cock-and-bull story ‘bout the war between the Mages and the Necromancers lately. Sure I'm not overfond of the undead, but the deeds of those old Necromancers command some respect. For instance, one of them, he managed to hold his town for long by simply not allowing the enemy armies to join. See, he just fought them one after another! And he held out! Guess why I’m talking ‘bout that? It’s cause our situation is much like the same. Maybe we should use the same tactics, eh?