It is 951, and whispers of a Demon invasion appear to be more than mere rumours. The Griffin Empire desperately needs an alliance with the Silver Cities for the upcoming war. However, old enmities between the two kingdoms get in the way. Godric must find a way to convince the Wizards to change their mind, and thereby enlist their support. To do that, he must find the Pendant of Mastery hidden in Dragon Utopia. This relic will serve as a sign of reconciliation between the peoples. It goes without saying that Godric must avoid at all costs a clash with the potential ally's troops.