Not every dweller of the cursed villages worships demons, but to acheive great goals innocents must occasionally suffer.  Laszlo believes that eliminating all who can possibly be concerned with the cult is the only practical method. Freyda disagrees, and is willing to spend time saving the innocent. Perhaps these people, who will owe their lives to the young commander, may some day repay their debt. 