For many years the Elves kept the secret of this town and its mine of crystals, with which they created marvelous jewelry and items of power.  During the War of the Blood Moon the secret was revealed, but it turned out to be exceedingly difficult for anyone but the Elves to master this art. Since that time the miners here openly produce crystals, which the Elves require for their magical rites and artifacts.