As Nightshard lost its first city, the panic began to spread (a good sign). But there is a bad side to this situation, Nightshard will now surely try to ally itself with the powerful Soulscar Clan .<br>A war with the Soulscar  could upset Realag's plans, and he must stop all messengers who could escape to reach their  territory. Luckily it is known that messengers will follow Nothern and Western roads that lay not far from entrance from dungeon.