Talanar was the only survivor of one of the brutal attacks on The Day of the Tears of Fire.  Seeing hundreds of his kinsmen die staggered the young warrior, and filled him with an insatiable rage that returns whenever he sees his brethren fall in battle.  His zeal for revenge is so great that it passes to those who are near him, the greater the losses suffered by his troops, the fiercer they become.