Rutger was mostly known as a vagabond, free spirit, and traveler before the call to arms brought him into the ranks of the Falcon Empire's Wolf Duchy. Using the knowledge gained during his more carefree years, Rutger exploits every path, trail, and shortcut to speed his troops from battle to battle. The sooner he finishes the war, the sooner he can return to the roads that still seem to call his name.