In 568, two years after the Day of the Tears of Fire and the subsequent death of their leader Tuidhana, Dark Elf exiles were still searching for a new homeland. Scattered and embattled, they were hunted mercilessly by their Sylvan brethren who sought revenge for the destruction of their Sacred Tree and the murder of the High King.
Eruina, a leader and hero of the Dark Elves, hoped to find solace on Farwind Island and make peace with her neighbors. She signed a treaty with Rutger, leader of a town of humans, but the Humans betrayed her and sent word to the Elves -- their old allies -- that she was in hiding there with her kin. Spies informed her that a fleet captained by the Elven hero Talanar would leave to hunt down the Dark Elves. Worse yet, Eruina's life is complicated by Sinitar, an ambitious and jealous Dark Elf neighbor. Rumors hint that he has been driven to madness by his dealings with the Shadow Dragons.
Eruina must first take control of the caverns of the Dark Elves, then revenge herself on Rutger for his betrayal. Finally, when Talanar and his fleet arrive, she must be prepared to defend her home at all costs…