You ever think just why Isabel decided to make an alliance with Necromancers? What's in it for her? Well, I did, and here's what I think: she wants to resurrect Nicolai! If she pulls that off she'd shut up everybody who's unhappy with her rule, and have her own hands free to destroy the Demons that she hates... Well, I say, good for her! I'd be willing to suffer a dead man on the throne if it helps get rid of the Demons!