Isabel has been captured by the enemy! Her only hope lies with Godric, who has returned from his mission to the Wizards of the Silver Cities. Though his diplomatic mission failed and he brings no new allies, he must still free the young queen from prison near the city of Dunmoor within a week.<br>Dunmoor, an old fortress which has survived many assaults, will provide a shelter for the queen in these troubled times.