The Dwarves' guerrilla warfare yields fruit. The Imperial legions’ advance has been stopped; they are occupied with gathering reinforcements and licking their wounds. The time is perfect to deliver a few hard blows, breaking their spirit and depriving them of supplies. Word will circulate across Ashan of the grim strength of the warriors of the Stone Halls, and the punishment they inflict on their foes.