In the year 820 of the Seventh Dragon's Creation, a Wizard named Maahir from the League of the Silver Cities undertook a perilous journey to Heresh. At that time Heresh, though under the control of the Necromancers, was a fertile and pleasant land. Maahir, however, had two grim objectives in mind: Eliminate Necromancer Zoltan, associate of Belketh with whom the League towns had been at war for 7 years, and retrieve four powerful artefacts that had disappeared from the Silver Cities. Few believed that Maahir's gamble would succeed, and nobody at all would have guessed that two years later he would have defeated Belketh and become First of the Circle, the supreme Archmage of the League of the Silver Cities.