The town I needed, but not this letter. "For the glory of Sylanna" - who writes tripe like this? Gilraen, of course. "The stain on my honor cannot be purged but by a ritual duel" - is this all they think about? I have more important things to do than reprimand petulant florists. Gilraen's welcome to become my enemy if he wishes, but he would do well to learn that those who make that choice seldom live to make too many others.