The rumors tell that Demonlord Agrael is skilled in all kinds of magic.<br>The time has come for Isabel to learn some secrets of the magical knowledge. Without it she will have little chances against the magical power of the Demonlord.<br>Brightwood is well-known for its Magic Guilds - the perfect place for the young queen, who has disided to fight her enemies not only with the power of steel. Isabel should prepare  the attack on Brightwood properly. Time is not important.