Rumour has it that Demon Lord Agrael is skilled in the ways of magic.<br>The time has come for Isabel also to learn the secrets of arcane lore, for without this knowledge she will have difficulty facing the magics of the Demon Lord.<br>Brightwood was well-known for its Magic Guilds - a perfect place for the young queen to study the magical arts.  Isabel must prepare  the attack on Brightwood properly, success is more important than time. Capture Brightwood and upgrade its Magic Guild to the third level