Night Everlasting envelops the lands controlled by the Undead, allowing Nicolai to rise again and again. The Seer says that this problem can be solved if Phoenix are present in the army. He has some and can give them to Findan if the latter fulfils his condition and finds the ancient Dwarven artifacts: Cuirass of the Dwarven Kings, Greaves of the Dwarven Kings, Shield of the Dwarven Kings and Helmet of the Dwarven Kings - The Seer believes that only the hero who can manage to collect all these artifacts deserves possession of such majestic creatures as Phoenix.