More ears than those of the Demon Sovereign heard Thralsai’s prayers. Malassa, the Dragon of Shadow and the patroness of the Dark Elves, listened in anger and removed her blessings from her people.  As a result the Shadow and Black Dragons, their strongest creatures, serve the Warlocks no more. But there is a way to summon them again, if Ylaya can prove herself worthy. The Daughter of Malassa (Black Dragon) shouldn't leave Ylaya's army to be under protection and, of course, it must survive.