Though the universe as we know it was founded by Asha, the Mother, her six dragon offspring were instrumental in developing the peoples of her world. One such person grew so great in wisdom and power that he, Sar-Elam, became the Seventh Dragon.  Much of his power passed on to his greatest disciple, Sar-Issus, and when he in turn passed on, Sar-Issus left behind relics of unimaginable power -- Robe of Sar-Issus, Crown of Sar-Issus, Ring of Sar-Issus, and Staff of Sar-Issus. When Maahir gets all these artifacts he will become a force to be reckoned with...