The Demon Sovereign is dead! So who will rule Sheog? Who will dare become Urgash’s deputy in this world? Veyer knows this lucky one’s name. He is the only possessor of the secret knowledge, and isn’t going to miss his chance. The only thing he has to do is learn the right things and obtain three artifacts seized by stupid Men and Elves who have been so bold as to erect their settlements in the Demon’s native lands. They won’t have to wait for long: the new Sovereign is coming!