The year is 751, after a brutal civil war between the Wizards and the Necromancers that has split the nation of magic-users in two. The Necromancers, driven from their homes by armies summoned by their Wizard brethren, are seeking a land to call their own. They are settling in the largely unoccupied territories known as Heresh, a large and fertile peninsula of land surrounded by a numerous archipelagi. Raven, a Necromancer seeking to resume her studies in peace, has discovered an island that will suit her well and renamed it "Obiira." Unfortunately, restarting her life will not be that simple. Neighboring islands belong to hostile enemies, and an armada of vengeful Wizards still hunts her. It will be some time before the sound of rustling papers and incantations replaces the crash of steel and the cries of the dying...