As soon as necromancer left, Godric started his own game in order to prevent plans of Markal and Isabel come true. The betrayer locked himself in Hikm, blocked the sea-lane, destroyed the portal which lead to town and refused to give back the Amulet of Necromancy. Markal will have to find the way to capture Hikm and return the Amulet. And he has to do it quick because Godric is about to destroy the Amulet. The Amulet can be destroyed in the Night of Triple Lunar Eclipse. Unfortunately, this night will come in a month.