Good luck accompanies the dwellers of Asbrand both in peaceful labor and in war. This is because of a magical sword, Asbrand’s pride and chief of its treasures. A legend says that the runes adorning the ancient blade are the marks left by the breath of Akatosh himself, who gave this sword to the first of the Dwarves and promised to grant the Mountain Folk his protection and help in all their undertakings.