The Dwarves, they lose and retreat. I’ll say! There’s such a horde pushing at ‘em, sure they can’t hold out. Makes me wonder why the King of Dwarves is just hacking around. If all the Dwarves gathered together and approached in force, they'd be a force to be reckoned with. But he  stays locked up in his capital and gives no help to the frontier clans -- not in word or in deed. This all is weird, really weird!