In the year of 954 YSD, three peaceful years after the end of the Fifth Eclipse war, the Irollan Elves announced a big festival for the heroes of that bloody conflict. One of these heroes was Dougal, a commander of the late king Alexei Griffin, who decided to take part in the Archery tournament. Dougal found peacetime a bit boring, and figured that an archery contest would be just the thing to add a bit of excitement to his life. After all, his skills were only needed for entertainment in those pleasant days - there was no sign of trouble on the horizon at all...