As dedicated as his comrades to the glory of the Griffin Empire, Dougal's loyalty is balanced with a strong dose of pragmatism. Believing that the best enemy is one that is dead before he can lay a hand on a Griffin soldier, Dougal has specialized for many years in the training and equipping of archers. The shooters return his faith, believing that little can endanger them while Dougal is in command.