The echoes of the latest War of the Eclipse swept over the world like a mighty wave, and some used that to their advantage. Yrbeth, the child-prodigy among the Dark Elf Warlocks, took advantage of Findan’s absence and seized a number of Elven towns. Their inhabitants dead, the towns are now controlled by Elementals summoned by the powerful Witch. Findan has come back from war, but will not be able to rest. Duty demands that he liberate the occupied towns and defeat this enemy before his war is truly over.