Founded in the far-off year 62 of the Seventh Dragon's Creation, the secret Order of Dragon Knights has been dedicated to protecting the world of Ashan from the Demon scourge.  But the Third Eclipse War called their very existence into question: many of the Dragon Knights were killed, their secret havens destroyed. The Order needs new novices, but few have what is required to devote their life to the secret struggle - not by a long shot. Only the wisest and the most patient will be able to pass the Riddles Test that the head of the Order arranges for his future associates.