Lord of the Necromancers Hefes, in a moment of great urgency, had to gather a mighty army at short notice. He spent 4000 gold to gather this army, recruited from Vampires, Liches, and Zombies. You must build an army that is a precise copy of Hefes's army, given the facts that to recruit one lich costs 100 gold, one vampire costs 70 gold, and one zombie a mere 40 gold. It is recorded that there were a quarter more zombies than vampires and a quarter more vampires than liches.