If you wish a challenge, try this.  Create an army containing the smallest possible number of these high level creatures : Angels, Devils, Bone Dragons and Collossi. Note that Devils fight better if there are more Bone Dragons than Collossi, and Collossi are fiercer if there are fewer Collossi then Devils. And Angels will fight only of there are more Angels than there are Devils and Bone Dragons put together.