Army balance is critical to victory. It is well known that Peasants are not fond of Imps, and the number of Peasants must be at least twice the number of Imps. Hunters can't stand Gremlins, and will fight only if there are five times more Hunters than Gremlins in the army. Gremlins are also quite touchy, they will fight well only if there are ten times more Imps in the army -- that shows a feat of courage when defended by the group of Hunters two times less then the number of Imps. Build me army with all of the mentioned units that fight well, do not have any grudges against each other, and contains at least 20 peasants.