It is 823, and the War of the Broken Staff that saw the destruction of the Necromancer Kingdom of Heresh has ended. The Kingdom of the Dead is destroyed, the great Belketh is dead, and his pupils are despised and exiled. Many of them are in hiding, others are trying vainly to resist. Others still, like Necromancer Naadir, are looking for answers in the long-lost wisdom of Sar-Elam and Sar-Shazzar.  Naadir undertakes a long and perilous quest, based on information he obtained from an ancient parchment, to find an unsullied copy of the original teachings of the Seventh Dragon.