That’s what I say, milord: I know nothing of what’s going on in the Dwarves’ capital, but the Dwarves, they’ve never given quarter to their offenders. The King of the Mountain made peace with Queen Isabel all right, but the war ain’t going to be over soon. There’s only one way: either all the Dwarves are dead or they reach Talonguard herself and give ‘em all a good scolding there. Such a folk they are!